Alright, everyone, enjoy
the rest of your vacation.
Next semester, let's...
Yoo Chae-min.
How can you keep doing
this till the very end?
How on earth did you get an A?
I'm sorry.
It's so unfair.
[Episode 15]
[Dear My Summer]
What?
You said you were up
watching NBA until late.
But why am I the only
one who's tired?
Come on, be honest.
Didn't you just
watch the highlights?
Why don't you just
criticize me?
Yoo Chae-min.
Thanks for the USB
it was really helpful.
Hold on a second.
Did you see it by any chance?
What?
A photo of you two?
Hey, Choi Min-seo.
You look great
in photos, Se-woon.
So, we're planning
to go there today too.
We'll be off now.
I'm really sorry
for the 53rd time.
54th time.
I'm truly sorry
for the 55th time.